Kettle and Idols
Now I'd like to go to the main project.
I'd like to ask you to do the title call, and I'd like to ask you to do the title call in a cute way.
Yes, my three main elements
Ooh! Cute!
Yeah!
Now, this corner is for you to introduce the three elements that make up Ueda-san!
Yes, sir!
Let's get to know our guest idols better!
Now, please tell us the three elements that make up Ms. Ueda.
Let's see!
Karate
2. comedy
3. talkativeness.
Karate.
This is a well-known idol of Mr. Ueda.
I'd like to hear more about what you have to say.
Yes.
My father taught karate.
So I followed him.
Really?
That's right.
I started when I was about 4 or 5 years old.
So you've been here a long time.
I have a third-degree black belt.
3rd Dan? That's amazing.
That's right.
But I'm not so good at kumite fighting.
I'm better at kata.
You mean the ones you see in the Olympics?
That's right.
I just think it's so cool.
No, it's cool.
It's really cool.
And I love the sound of the dojis rubbing against each other.
I really like the sound of the dojis rubbing against each other.
I want to make that sound.
It's so cool, isn't it?
That's the type of sound I want to make.
Have you ever done it in front of an audience wearing street clothes?
I've never done it in Doyi.
I see.
Is that something you have in mind?
No, not at all.
It's not that I don't have any.
It's funny that I don't have any feelings about it.
I earned a black belt in elementary school.
I already have a real black belt.
My real black belt was rubbed off and turned white.
A lie.
I can't really show it to you because it's in shreds.
So I can get a new one.
a proper black belt.
I have a black belt
but I don't get a chance to show it.
Well, I don't have a chance to show it to you. Well, when do you have a chance to show it?
Is it the 10th anniversary of the book of punishment, or is it the same thing?
Well, it would be cool if we could put some spotlight on it.
Then I'll practice hard for two years from now.
Really. You're going to show me something like that so casually?
I'm just being casual.
But I've been showing it almost exclusively for the past eight years now, so I'm just saying the opposite.
That's right. That's right. If you think about it...
I've heard Ueda-san karate karate various episodic talks, but
But I haven't seen him do it once, so I was a bit suspicious of him, wasn't I?
You are being doubted. It's true.
I can't do any other sports except karate.
That's why you're so athletic.
Athleticism, too.
You can dance too?
Yes.
I'm not very athletic.
That's why I don't think people trust me.
I see.
But, you know... like in the Olympics...
You know, something really sophisticated.
You don't mind if I imagine it, do you?
Yes, it's fine.
For our part.
We're going to practice hard for the next two years.
Can I ask the manager for a few minutes?
I'd like to see it sometime.
Please come and see us someday. You too, kettle.
No, no, no.
At the audition for the Stargate office.
I did a karate routine.
Did you do that?
I did,
A lot of aspiring idols and singers do that, so...
Of course they do.
It was a big scene, and I thought I had failed.
No, you didn't.
It was an open audition.
It was open to the public.
There was an audience.
I don't know... when you were there, there were a lot of calls for you.
but only when it was me.Only when it's me.
I know you guys are trying to be considerate and quiet, but
I just thought it was so quiet.
I thought, "I fell.
I was thinking, "Oh, my God.
Regardless of whether it's because I'm a big name or not.
But whatever you think is fine.
Well, you know, Rainey, who I like the best...
This show...
Ms. Luster.
Saki
Mohi
Nukusho DD Keisuke Taisuke-san